power.com 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Power Integrations

Power Integrations, Inc. ("Company") has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. Your privacy on Company’s web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our users, we have established a means to communicate to our users how we use and handle the information collected. This Privacy Policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

**Collected Information**  
Company permits users of the Site to input certain personally identifiable information ("User Information"). Company uses the User Information to provide services requested by the user (the "Services") and to send users information regarding Company and its products. You can choose not to receive such information or Services by notifying Company as set forth below in the "Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy. Company may also use the User Information according to the Website User Agreement which can be found on the Site.

As a user of the Site, we may collect certain information about you, including your Internet address. This information is logged to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Services. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our users, and provide such information to Company’s affiliates (as defined in the Website User Agreement) to comply with various reporting obligations and for business or marketing purposes. Company does not sell or rent your information to third parties.

**Third Party Sites**  
The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet. Company is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of, the user agreement of, or the content of such sites. You will need to check the user agreement and the privacy policy statement of such other sites to understand their policies and practices. In interacting with such sites you may be sharing private information with such sites. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.

**Opt-Out**  
If at any time you decide that you do not want Company to share your information with Company’s affiliates, simply send your request to webmaster@powerint.com with the words "User Opt Out" in the subject or re line so that we can process your request promptly.

**Privacy Policy Changes  
** Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Company will post any changes here so that our users will know what information Company gathers, how it might use that information and whether it will disclose such information to third parties.
